嘿 艾迪
Hey, Eddie. Aah!
- 你在这里做什么？ - 没事 看你睡觉
- What are you doing here?     - Watching you sleep.
为什么？
Why?
那让我觉得很宁静
It makes me feel, um, peaceful.
请继续
Ha, ha. Ahem. Please.
现在我睡不着了
I can't sleep now!
你要我唱歌给你听吗？
Oh, you want me to sing?
不 听着
No. Look.
够了 我要你立刻离开这间公寓
That's it. I want you out of the apartment now!
你在胡说什么？
Oh, what are you talking about?
人魔汉尼拔
Hannibal Lecter?
他比你更适合当室友
Better roommate than you.
不
No.
我觉得你不公平 某天晚上你看到我 觉得很可怕
I don't think you're being fair! One night you see me, you get scared.
你没看到我的那些晚上呢？
What about the other nights when you don't see me, huh?
昨晚你起床喝水
Last night you went and got some water...
我好心地躲在门后 那又如何？
and I was nice enough to hide behind the door. What that about, huh?
- 我不知道   - 噢
- I didn't realize that.     - Ah.
快给我滚
Get out now!
好吧 你真的要我滚吗？
Okay. You really want me out?
对 请滚
Yes, please.
我要听你说你要我滚
Then I want to hear you say you want me out.
我要你滚
I want you out.
我要听你亲口说
I want to hear it from your lips.
那之前你从哪里听来的？
Where'd you hear it before?
好吧 你知道吗？就当我已经滚了
Oh, right, all right. You know what? Consider me gone.
明天你下班回来会发现我不在了
I'll be out by the time you get home from work tomorrow.
- 谢谢   - 我听到了
- Thank you.     - I heard that.
没有人告诉你活着有多累
∮ So no one told you life was gonna be this way ∮
上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘
∮ Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. ∮
寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累
∮ It's like you're always stuck in second gear ∮
日复一日 年复一年
∮ When it hasn't been your day, ∮
时运不济 活着受罪
∮ your week, your month, or even your year ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ but I'll be there for you ∮
纵有狂风暴雨
∮ When the rain starts to pour ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ I'll be there for you ∮
支持一如往昔
∮ Like I've been there before ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ I'll be there for you ∮
你我相偎相依
∮ 'Cause you're there for me too ∮
- 谢谢   - 嘿
- Thanks.     - Hey.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
看看你
Well, look at you!
终于把时光机修好了？
Finally got that time machine working, huh?
你们喜欢吗？
You like it?
有个家伙在第八大道卖衣服 我心想
This guy was selling them on 8th Avenue and I thought:
- "你知道我没有什么吗？"   - 镜子？
- "You know what I don't have?"     - A mirror?
好吧 尽量开玩笑 我觉得这个造型蛮潇洒的
Fine, make fun. I think it's jaunty.
对刚失业的人来说 你的心情蛮不错的
Wow! For a guy who's recently lost his job, you're in a good mood.
我会没事的 我又不是从头开始
I'll be all right. I'm not starting from square one.
我在《我们的日子》 饰演过德瑞克雷莫瑞医生
I was Dr. Drake Ramoray on Days of our Lives.
那应该有某种关连吧
Huh? That's got to have some kind of cachet.
关连？潇洒？
Cachet? Jaunty?
钱德送我每日一字卫生纸
Chandler gave me word-of-the-day toilet paper.
我去买杯咖啡
I'm gonna get some coffee.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
所以呢？你看那本书了吗？
Oh! So? Did you read the book?
天啊 太不可思议了
Oh, my God. It was incredible!
它真的说中你的心声了吧？
Didn't it, like, totally speak to you?
- 这是什么样的书？ - 噢
- Whoa, whoa, what book is this?     - Oh.
瑞秋 你一定要看这本书 书名是《做自己的追风人》
Uh! You have to read this book. It's called Be Your Own Wind Keeper.
描述女性必须更有力量
Ooh. It's about how women need to become more empowered.
还有风
And, oh! But there's wind.
风让我们成为女神
And the wind can make us goddesses.
你知道谁把我们的风抢走了吗？男人 他们抢走风了
Do you know who takes our wind? Men. They just take it.
男人抢走风了？
Men just take our wind?
一直都是的 因为他们是闪电人
Uh-huh. All the time. Because they are the lightning-bearers.
- 哇   - 耶
- Wow.     - Yeah.
那听起来很酷 蛮像哈比人的
That sounds kind of cool. It's like The Hobbit.
一点都不像
It is nothing like The Hobbit.
它像是看穿了我的每段恋情
It's like reading about every relationship I've ever had.
理查除外
Except for Richard.
理查不会抢走你的风
Oh, yes. No. Richard would never steal your wind.
- 没错   - 没错
- No.     - No.
- 因为他是帅哥   - 没错
- Because he's yummy.     - Yes.
但其他男人就会
But all the other ones.
有一段描述他们不断地吸干
Oh, and the part about how they're always drinking...
我们的内心力量
from our pool of inner power.
但上帝禁止我们使用内心力量
But God forbid we should take a sip.
谁要吃油条？
Anybody want a cruller?
这是闪电人的典型作法
This is a typical lightning-bearer thing.
那像是…
Right there. It's like, um...
"谁要吃我的老二形状蛋糕"？
"Hello. Who wants one of my phallic-shaped man-cakes?"
别担心 情况很不错
Don't worry about it, already! Things happen.
所以你不气我被开除？
So you're not mad at me for getting fired and everything?
乔伊 看着我
Joey, look at me.
看着我
Look at me!
我的牙齿沾到口红了吗？
Do I have lipstick on my teeth?
没有
No.
我们能继续谈我的问题吗？
Uh, can we get back to me?
听着 在这一行常有人被开除
Look, honey. People get fired left and right in this business.
我已经帮你争取到 《未来日记》试镜机会
I already got you an audition for Another World.
太棒了
All right!
"二号计程车司机"？
"Cab Driver Number 2"?
不客气
You're welcome.
但我演过德瑞克雷莫端医生
But... But I was Dr. Drake Ramoray!
我怎么从神经外科医生 变成开计程车的？
How can I go from being a neurosurgeon to driving a cab?
时代会改变 接受吧
Things change. Roll with them.
但这个角色只有两句台词
But this is a two-line part!
这是在退步
It's like taking a step backwards.
我才不要这份工作
I'm not gonna do this.
乔伊
Joey.
我跟你说的话就像我跟阿尔明查
I'm gonna tell you the same thing I told Al Minza...
还有他的狗狗金字塔说的话一样
and his pyramid of dogs.
有工作就做 别在地上大便
Take any job you can get, and don't make on the floor.
对不起
I'm sorry.
再见
I'll see you.
天啊
Uh, God!
天啊 我是说它真的…
Oh, God! I mean, it's just so...
对吧？
Isn't it?
这像是在看我的一生
Uh. This is like reading about my own life!
这本书应该叫 《做你自己的追风人 瑞秋》
This book could have been called Be Your Own Wind Keeper, Rachel!
虽然会卖不了一百万本
It wouldn't have sold a million copies...
但那会是送你很不错的礼物
but it would've made a nice gift for you.
- 大家好   - 嘿
- Hey, you guys.     - Hey.
甜心 我们该走了
Uh, sweetie, we've gotta go.
不
No!
不？
No? Heh.
不 为什么我们总得 照你的时间表来做事？
No! Why do we always have to do everything according to your timetable?
事实上那是电影院的时间表
Actually, it's the movie theater that has the timetable.
这样你才不会错过开头
It's so you don't miss the beginning.
不 这跟电影院无关 问题是你抢走我的风了
This isn't about the movie theater. This is about you stealing my wind.
加油 好姊妹
You go, girl!
我做得很不像吧？
I can't pull that off, can I?
对不起 你的风？
Excuse me, your wind?
对 我的风
Yes, my wind.
你不让我吹 又怎么能期待成长？
How do you expect me to grow if you won't let me blow?
你知道我…
You know I don't...
可以接受你那么做
have a problem with that.
好吧
Okay.
现在我需要独处一下
I just really need to be with myself right now.
对不起
I'm sorry.
- 呃   - 你们说的对
- Mm, mm, mm.     - Uh, you're right.
我不必道歉
I don't have to apologize.
抱歉 该死
Sorry. Damn it!
- 那是什么？ - 我不知道
- What is it?     - I don't know.
里面提到风跟树
It's got all this stuff about wind and trees...
还有圣池
and some sacred pool.
我看不懂 但她似乎非常生气
I don't really get it. But she's pretty upset about it.
所以我不跟会看书的女人约会
This is why I don't date women who read.
啊哦
Uh-oh.
什么？那是什么？
What? What's that?
我的信用卡帐单
It's my VISA bill.
一式两联
Envelope one of two.
- 这不会是好事   - 快打开
- That can't be good.     - Open it, open it.
- 天啊   - 哇
- Oh, my God!     - Whoa!
看看这个 我怎么会花这么多钱？
Look at this! How did I spend so much money?
乔伊 那是最低应缴额度 总额在那边
Uh, that's just the minimum amount. That's your total.
啊
Aah!
在"原野瓷器"刷了三千五？
Whoa, whoa. Thirty-five hundred dollars at "Porcelain Safari"?
我的动物们
My animals.
店员说它们很适合我 他说起话来有口音 我很困惑
The guy said they suited me. He spoke with an accent. I was confused.
噢
Oh.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do!
你可以开始 在《未来日记》开计程车
You can start by driving a cab on Another World.
- 什么？ - 那个试镜机会？
- What?     - That audition?
那个角色只有两句台词
That's a two-line part!
乔伊 你在"我爱透明塑胶玻璃"欠下一千一百块
Joey, you owe $1100 at "I Love Lucite."
- 那又怎么样？ - 接受吧
- So what?     - So suck it up, man.
那是工作 可以赚钱
It's a job. It's money.
我不要你变得爱批评 高傲又爱卖弄学问
I don't need you getting judgmental and condescending and pedantic.
- 来自卫生纸？ - 对
- Toilet paper?     - Yeah.
我不是那样的人 我只是很现实
I'm not being any of those things. I'm being realistic.
- 不必了 你应该是我的朋友   - 我是你的朋友
- You're supposed to be my friend!     - I am your friend.
那你该跟我说"你会没事的"
Then tell me things like, "You'll be fine."
"你一定会出头的 我知道"
And "Something big's gonna come along. I know it!"
但我真的不知道
But I don't know it.
我只知道你在"漂亮着色"欠下两千三百块钱
What I do know is you owe $2300 at "Isn't It Chromantic?"
罗斯 我知道我欠了多少钱
I'm aware of what I owe.
你得有点理智 你等了十年才找到那份工作
Then get some sense. It took you 10 years to get that job.
- 下份工作又得等多久呢？ - 我不想听
- How long till you get another?     - I don't want to hear this!
我只是说…
I'm just saying...
别"只是说"
Well, don't "just say"!
或许我该先离开
Oh. Maybe I should just go.
好吧
Okay.
待会见
I'll see you later.
考虑一下
Just think about it.
我不需要考虑
I don't need to think about it!
我是德瑞克雷莫瑞医生
I was Dr. Drake Ramoray!
那是重要角色
That was huge!
我的大好机会一定会出现 等着瞧吧
Big things are gonna happen! You'll see!
罗斯
Ross!
你还在吗？
You still there?
- 嘿 朋友   - 噢 天呐
- Hey, pal.     - Oh, God!
你还在这里做什么？
What are you still doing here?
帮蔬菜跟水果脱水
Uh, just some basic dehydrating of fruits and vegetables.
天啊 这真的太棒了
Man alive, this thing's fantastic!
艾迪 你是不是忘了什么？
Aren't you forgetting anything?
对了 我帮我们买了新金鱼
Oh, yeah. I got us a new goldfish.
他比上一只金鱼还有活力
He's feistier than the last one.
或许因为上一只金鱼 是培珀莉饼干做的
Maybe because the last one was made by Pepperidge Farm.
艾迪 你是不是忘了做什么事？
Eddie, isn't there something else you're supposed to be doing now?
不 除非它跟脱水有关
Not unless it's got something to do with dehydrating.
因为现在我是脱水迷
Because right now, I'm a dehydrating maniac!
我以为我们说好了
I thought we had a deal.
- 我以为我回来时…   - 呃
- I thought by the time I got...     - Uh, uh.
你知道这是什么吗？
You know what that is?
你前室友的肾脏？
Your last roommate's kidney?
这是蕃茄
That's a tomato. Ha, ha.
这应该拿出来公开展示
This one definitely goes in the display.
这需要公开展示
It's in the display.
阿甘 我要外带一杯柠檬汁
Hey, Gunther. Let me get a, uh, lemonade to go.
柠檬汁？
Lemonade?
你没事吧？
You okay, man?
只是事业遇到瓶颈
Ahh, it's career stuff.
他们将我在影集里的角色赐死
They killed off my character on the show.
那太可惜了 他们是怎么做的？
Oh, that's too bad. How'd they do it?
我跌落电梯里
I fell down an elevator shaft.
那真的很逊
Oh. That sucks.
我被雪崩掩埋
I was buried in an avalanche.
什么？
What?
我演过《我的孩子们》里 布莱斯的角色
I used to be Brice on All My Children.
为什么大家都要看我睡觉？
Why must everybody watch me sleep?
不准再看我睡觉了 不准…
There'll be no more watching me sleep! No more...
- 再看了   - 我…
- watching!     - I...
那
Neh.
我帮一些东西做脱水 葡萄 杏桃
I got some great stuff to dehydrate. Grapes, apricots.
我觉得这会是个好点子 看看这些水球会变成什么样子
I thought it'd be cool to see what happens with these water balloons.
滚出去…
Get out. Get out, get out, get out!
- 什么？ - 你给我搬出去
- What?     - You! Move out!
带着你的愚蠢脱水水果滚出去
Take your fruit! Your stupid small fruit and get out!
你要我搬走？
You want me to move out? Uh...
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
嗨 我 呃...
Heh. I, uh...
我得说你不觉得那有点突然吗？
Ooh! Ha, ha. I gotta tell you, that's kind of out of the blue, don't you think?
这一点都不突然
This is not out of the blue!
这完全都不突然
This is smack-dab in the middle of the blue!
哇
Whoa!
放轻松 别激动
Relax! Take it easy, buddy!
你不必告诉我第二次
You don't have to tell me twice.
天啊 我会找人来搬我的东西
God, I mean, someone will be by for my stuff.
如果你以为我会让你跟我的鱼独处 你就疯了
If you think I'm leaving you alone with my fish, you're insane!
需要我帮忙吗？
You want some help?
我不需要帮忙 朋友
No help required, chico!
一路直达机场？那超过三十里远
All the way to the airport, huh? You know, that's over 30 miles.
那得花你不少钱
That's gonna cost you about so bucks.
对不起 应该是"五十"块
Excuse me, that's "50" bucks.
- 什么？ - 五十块
- What?     - Fifty dollars.
你知道这是怎么一回事吗？传真过来的剧本字体有点模糊
Oh. You know what it is? It's smudgy because they're fax pages.
我在《我们的日子》 演德瑞克雷莫瑞医生时
When I was on Days ofour Lives as Dr. Drake Ramoray...
他们会把完整剧本寄过来给我
they'd send over the whole script on real paper.
那真的太棒了
Ha, ha. That's great.
如果你要加戏 譬如让计程车发生车祸
If you wanted to expand this scene, like have the cab crash...
我可以治疗乘客
I could attend to the victims...
因为我有演医生的背景
because I have a background in medical acting.
好吧 听我说 谢谢你来试镜
Okay, listen, thanks for coming in.
不 别谢我来试镜 至少让我演完
No. Uh, don't thank me for coming in. Uh, at least let me finish.
我们可以走快速道路
Uh, we could take the expressway...
但这时你很可能会超过预算
but, uh, this time of day you're better off taking the budge.
应该是要过桥才对吧？
You were going for bridge there, weren't you?
我自己出去
I'll have a good day.
好吧 第28题
Okay, question number 28.
"你曾让闪电人抢走你的风吗？"
"Have you ever allowed a lightning-bearer to take your wind?"
我要回答"没有"
I would have to say no.
我的答案是"胡扯"
And I would have to say, "Pah, ha."
什么？
What?
你不记得布偶男了吗？
Do you not remember the puppet guy?
你让他在你的内心力量池洗脚
You totally let him wash his feet in the pool of your inner power.
还有他的布偶
And his puppet too!
至少我没有让男人
Well, at least I didn't let some guy...
在第一次约会时进入我的真理森林
into the forest of my righteous truth on the first date!
- 谁？ - 保罗
- Who?     - Paul!
噢
Oh!
好吧 继续 下一题
Okay, okay, moving on, moving on. Next question.
好吧 第29题
Okay, number 29.
"你曾为了闪电人
"Have you ever betrayed another goddess...
背叛其他女神吗？"好吧 第30题
for a lightning-bearer?" Okay, number 30.
喔…回到第29题
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Let's go back to 29.
不是 呃...
Not, uh...
在我的记忆里是没有
Ahem. Not to my recollection.
丹尼亚夏克 九年级
Danny Arshack, ninth grade.
你知道瓶口是指向我
You know the bottle was pointing at me.
那是因为你占了一半的空间
Only because you took up half the circle!
看看你们两个 真是可悲
Listen to you two. It's so sad.
哦
Oh!
看起来我得一个人参加女神会议
Looks like I'll be going to the goddess meetings alone.
唔
Mm.
你休想 当她们发现杰森跟摩妮卡分手一小时后
Not when they find out you slept with Jason...
你就跟他上床
an hour after he broke up with Monica.
一小时？
One hour?
- 你是个抓耙子   - 噢
- You are such a leaf blower!     - Oh!
噢
Ugh!
Ugh.
小心3D版《最后晚餐》
Oh, hey, uh, be careful with that 3-D Last Supper.
犹大有点松了
Judas is a little loose.
天啊 发生了什么事？
Oh, my God! What's going on?
他们要把我的东西收回去 我想你说得对
They're taking all my stuff back. I guess you were right.
不 我错了 所以我来找你
No, I wasn't right. That's what I came here to tell you.
那天我满脑子只想着自己的事
I was totally hung up on my own stuff the other day.
不 听着 我非常需要安全感
No, listen. I need the whole security thing, you know?
知道下一笔收入在哪里 但你不需要那么做
To know where my next paycheck is coming from. But you don't need that.
那真的让我很佩服
And that's amazing to me.
我永远都没办法跟你一样 乔伊
I could never do what you do.
- 谢谢   - 你有伟大梦想
- Thanks.     - You hold out for something bigger.
我无法告诉你我多么尊重
I can't tell you how much respect I have...
你不去参加那个愚蠢的试镜
for you not going to that stupid audition.
- 我去了   - 太棒了 结果如何？
- I went.     - Great! How did it go?
- 我没有被录取   - 太好了
- I didn't get it.     - Good for you!
你实现梦想
You're living the dream!
- 呵？ - 哈哈
- Huh?     - Ha, ha.
太棒了
All right, then!
- 别拿走我的鹦鹉   - 什么？
- Oh, not my parrot.     - What?
我看不下去了
I can't watch this.
等一下
Hey, hold on, hold on.
那只鸟要多少钱？
How much for the, uh? How much to save the bird?
－一千两百块   - 美金？
- Twelve hundred.     - Dollars?
你花一千两百块买只塑胶鸟？
You spent $1200 on a plastic bird?
那是一时冲动 它就在收银台附近
Uh, it was an impulse buy. Near the register.
把那只鸟带走
Go ahead with the bird.
- 有什么东西是两百块左右？ - 呃
- Do you have anything for around $200?     - Uh.
那只狗
The dog.
- 嗯？ - 对
- Huh?     - Yeah.
我买了
I'll take it.
这是我送你的礼物
My gift to you, man.
谢谢你 罗斯
Thanks, Ross!
但我真的喜欢那只鸟
I really liked that bird, though.
- 不过狗也可以   - 对
- But the dog! Oh!     - Yeah. Right?
蛋糕来了
Here are your cakes.
我们没有点蛋糕
We didn't order cake.
对 我知道 我请客
No, I know. Ahem. They're from me.
两位 这不是件好事
You guys, this is not good.
男人抢走我们的风已经够麻烦了
We have enough trouble with guys stealing our wind...
我们不该彼此对立
without taking it from each other.
- 你说的对   - 你知道吗？
- You're right.     - You know?
我爱你们这些女神
I love you goddesses.
我爱你
I love you.
我不想再抢你的风了
I don't ever want to suck your wind again.
噢
Oh.
- 谢谢 我们没事了吧？ - 我们没事了
- Thank you. So are we good?     - Oh. We're good.
- 我们没事了吧？ - 对
- We're good?     - Yes.
好吧 我得把蛋糕收回去 他们会扣我的薪水
Okay. Let me take these back. They'll take it out of my paycheck.
太棒了 那个疯子走了
Ding-dong, the psycho's gone!
- 这次你确定吗？ - 对
- Are you sure this time?     - Yes.
我真的看到他离开
I actually saw him leave.
那家伙在窗口拿着一颗假人头
That guy is holding a human head.
他在窗口拿着一颗假人头
He's holding a human head!
看吧 兄弟
Check it out, man!
我在梅西百货后面的巷子 从假人身上拔下来的
I tore it off a mannequin in the alley behind Macy's. Ha, ha.
梅西百货后面没有巷子
There is no alley behind Macy's.
我在少女百货偷来的 都一样啦
So I got it in the junior miss department. Big diff.
我们下一次办鸡尾酒会 这会是个不错的话题
It'll make a hell of a conversation piece at our next cocktail party, huh?
"我们下一次办鸡尾酒会"？
"Our next cocktail party"?
对 我们可以把薯片放进去 让它变成薯片小妞
Yeah, you know, we'll put chips in it. We'll make it a chip chick.
艾迪 你记得昨天吗？
Eddie, do you remember yesterday?
对 我依稀还记得
Uh, yes, I think I vaguely recall it.
你记得昨天你跟我说话吗？
Ahem. Do you remember talking to me yesterday?
对
Uh, yes.
发生了什么事？
So, what happened?
我们开车到拉斯维加斯
We took a road trip to Las Vegas!
天啊
Oh, sweet Moses!
你去拉斯维加斯有赢到钱吗？
So on this road trip, uh, did you win any money?
我输光光 但21点先生 他手气可好了
Nah, I crapped out. But Mr. 21 here! He cleans up!
三百块 他还送我这双新鞋子
$300! He buys me these new shoes. Sweet, huh?
太棒了
Nice.
楼上见 大家再见
Uh, see you upstairs. See you, pals!
有人开始喜欢他了吗？
Is anyone else starting to really like him?
有什么事需要我效劳吗？
May I help you?
为什么我的钥匙不能用？我的东西为什么在楼下？
Why doesn't my key work, and what's my stuff doing downstairs?
对不起
I'm sorry. Aah.
我们认识吗？
Have we met?
我是艾迪 变态 我是你的室友
It's Eddie, you freak! Your roommate.
对不起
I'm sorry, I, uh...
我已经有室友了
I already have a roommate.
你好
Hello.
他住在这里很多年 我不知道你到底在胡说什么
Um, he's lived here for years. I don't know what you're talking about.
不
No, no. He's, uh...
不 他搬出去 我搬进来
No, he moved out and I moved in.
我想我们会记得那种事
Well, I think we'd remember something like that.
我知道我会记得
I know I would. Ha, ha.
说得好
That's, uh, a good point. Um...
好吧
Okay, wow. Huh.
我想我走错门了
I guess I got the wrong apartment.
听着 我…
Look, I'm...
- 真的很抱歉   - 没关系
- I'm terribly sorry.     - Hey, no problem.
再见
See you.
再见 脱水水果变态狂
Goodbye, you fruit-drying psychopath.
- 要我帮你把东西拿出来吗？ - 不用了 我可以的
- You want me to help you unpack?     - Nah, I'm okay. Oh, and, uh...
你该知道我搬回来 不是因为我走投无路
Just so you know, I'm not moving back in because I have to.
我的确走投无路 可是…
I mean, I do have to, but...
那是因为那里不是…
It's just that that place, it wasn't really...
这是…
I mean, this is...
欢迎回家 兄弟
Welcome home, man.
- 玩一下足球台？ - 当然
- A little foos?     - Absolutely!
足球怎么了？
What happened to the foosball?
那是哈蜜瓜
It's a cantaloupe.
每次罗斯过来 我们都得把这个搬出来吗？
Are we gonna bring this out every time Ross comes over?
他付一大笔钱买下它的
He paid a lot of money for it.
- 我要转个方向   - 好吧
- I'm gonna hold him a different way.     - All right.
如果你那么讨厌它 一开始为什么要买下它？
If you hated it so much, why'd you buy it in the first place?
我买了一大堆瓷器动物摆在那里
Well, I had a whole ceramic-zoo thing going over there.
少了其他的动物 它看起来怪怪的
But without the other ones, it looks tacky.
它会使用马桶 或直接在浴室地板上？
Is he housetrained or will he leave little bathroom tiles all over?
别动
Stay.
Uh, stay!
好乖的假狗狗
Good fake dog.